<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Esscrypt</title><link>https://esscrypt.com/</link><description>Recent content on Esscrypt</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:43:12 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://esscrypt.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ProofPlus - Decentralized Prover Market</title><link>https://esscrypt.com/posts/decentralized-prover-market/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:10:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://esscrypt.com/posts/decentralized-prover-market/</guid><description>Potential solution to the current problem of centralized zkVM provers</description></item><item><title>Private Blockchain transactions</title><link>https://esscrypt.com/posts/private-transfers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://esscrypt.com/posts/private-transfers/</guid><description>Ethereum Proposal for implementation of plausibly deniable transfers</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://esscrypt.com/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://esscrypt.com/about/</guid><description>Who We Are Esscrypt is a software services provider that specializes in delivering innovative, robust, and scalable software solutions. Founded by a team of experienced technologists and visionaries, our mission is to empower businesses through the transformative power of modern software technologies.
What We Do At Esscrypt, we offer a comprehensive range of software services designed to meet the evolving needs of businesses across various industries. Our services include:
Custom Software Development: Tailored solutions that precisely fit the unique processes and objectives of your business.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://esscrypt.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 03:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://esscrypt.com/contact/</guid><description> We look forward to helping you achieve your business goals with precision-crafted software solutions tailored to your needs.
Your Email: Subject: Your message: Send Message</description></item><item><title>Prose</title><link>https://esscrypt.com/prose/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://esscrypt.com/prose/</guid><description>@tailwindcss/typography View on GitHub!
Beautiful typographic defaults for HTML you don&amp;rsquo;t control.
The official Tailwind CSS Typography plugin provides a set of prose classes you can use to add beautiful typographic defaults to any vanilla HTML you don’t control, like HTML rendered from Markdown, or pulled from a CMS.
Tailwind CSS IntelliSense extension for Visual Studio Code
&amp;lt;article class=&amp;#34;prose lg:prose-xl&amp;#34;&amp;gt;{{ markdown }}&amp;lt;/article&amp;gt; To see what it looks like in action, check out our live demo on Tailwind Play.</description></item></channel></rss>